McKersie, Robert Additional Files 6213
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert McKersie Additional Files
1990-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McKersie, Robert
6213
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Records.
8258626
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
McKersie, Robert
8258626
- Attendance (Box 1, Folder 1)
- People Pulse (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Pharmacy LMP Charter (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Working Agreements (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Lessons of the Geese (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Pharmacy LMP (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 25 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local 249 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- CCE 407 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Local 25 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 100 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Local 249 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 299 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Local 856 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Termination (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Appraisal (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Employment Law (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Drugs (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Negotiation (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Company (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Union (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Workplace Solutions (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Workplace Justice, "Zero Tolerance" (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Local 25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Local 100 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Local 170 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Local 135 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Local 249 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Local 287 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Local 299 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Local 407 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Local 600 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Local 671 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Local 856 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Exhibits (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Local 25 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Local 70 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 85 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Local 100 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Local 135 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Local 249 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Local 287 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Local 299 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Local 407 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Local 600 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Local 624 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Local 671 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Local 745 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Scholarships (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Presentation (Box 4, Folder 2)
- RP Conference (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Team (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Borse Cascade (Box 5, Folder 1)
- UAW NADA (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Pawtucket (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Exhibits (Box 5, Folder 4)
- State of Main (Box 5, Folder 5)
- W66N (Box 5, Folder 6)
- T. of Camillus vs. Camillus PBA etc. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- FMCS - Watervliet Arsenal vs. Nat. Asso. Govt. Employees Local R2-98 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Agreement- General Dynamics, Quincy Shipbuilding Division (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Arbitrations (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Cancelled (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mestel (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Boston Housing (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Agreement- Crocker Technical Papers, Inc. - United Paperworkers International Union Local no. 1102 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- In the Matter of Arbitration Between Worcester Polytechnic Institute and Local 254 Service Employees (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Coca-Cola and Teamsters Agreement (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Airline Studies (Box 7, Folder 1)
- American Arbitration Association (Box 7, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Arbitration - Strattec Security Corp. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- West Mass. Util (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Lake Superior (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Steel (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Steel (Box 8, Folder 3)
- General USW Pitts (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Board Sch (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Union Representation Campaign Literature Ryerson-Chicago (Box 8, Folder 6)
- An Orientation to Total Quality Management/Commitment (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Inland Steel Industries, Inc. - Nominating and Governance Committee, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  January 28, 1998
- Midwest Board Survey (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Comparison of Inland Board and Director Characteristics to Guidelines/Best Practices Identified by Corporate Governance Experts in Business Week Survey (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Steel - Idiot's Guide (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Managing to Win (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Inland Steel Industries 1993 Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Inland Steel Industries - Financial Statements and Operating Data, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  May 1994
- Inland Steel Industries 1992 Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Inland Steel Industries 1995 Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Annual Reports (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Strategic Initiative for Order Fulfillment (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Business Week - The Best and Worst Boards (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Inland Steel Industries, Inc. - Report to the Audit Committee of the Board of Directors, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  February 19, 1996
- IDC's 1997 Annual Plan and Strategic Direction (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Inland Steel Industries Reports (Box 9, Folder 12)
- My Letters/Reports (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Memorandum of Understanding between United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO-CIC and I/N Tek and I/N Kote, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  March 14, 1990
- Inland Steel Industries - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  September 24, 1997
- Altos Hornos de Mexico (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Inland Steel Industries, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology Files (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Inland Steel Industries - 1996 Annual Report (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Expenses (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Appointment Letter (Box 10, Folder 9)